Gabriel B. Casella

CONTACT INFORMATION http://gbc921.github.io

e-mail: gabrielbcasella@gmail.com

SKILLS **BACKGROUND**

Linux user since 2007 and Arch Linux user since 3 years ago, is really interested in system and network administration. Active member of the UTFPR open-source group that, for example, does a small Linux introduction to freshmen students. Also a fan of network and hardware, knows about ns-3 (wireless), iptables, NAT, web servers and wired/wireless protocols in general.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science

Expected graduation: 2014

Federal Technological University of Paraná

Ponta Grossa, PR, Brazil

Major: Computer Science

CAPES-CsF exchange student program:

Bachelor of Science January 2012 – December 2012

Western Michigan University

Kalamazoo, MI

Major: Computer Science

COMPUTER SKILLS

Linux, Lagrange C++, C++, C++, C++, Java, SQL, HTML5, JavaScript, CSS3, Office and Libre-Office, Virtualbox, ns-3.

EXPERIENCE

PROFESSIONAL UTFPR - Federal Technological University of Paraná, Ponta Grossa, Paraná, Brazil *Undergraduate Research* March 2011 - December 2011

- Worked with a desktop grid distributed system, written in Java focused on the balance of price integration among the cooperatives, the client and the server;
- Designed a simple Wordpress theme;
- Integrated PHP on Apache Tomcat.

EPROM, Bauru, São Paulo, Brazil

Computer Tech

January 2010 – March 2010

- Configured Windows systems to work properly, installing drivers, cleaning or reinstalling the system;
- Introduced backup/anti-virus check with a Linux Live CD instead of removing the hard drive from the computer and inserting it in the main computer. This made possible to do multiple scans/backup at the same time.